<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-25T20:22:08-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Meal at the End of the Day]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/25/my-favorite-meal-at-the-end-of-the-day/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-25T20:12:54-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/25/my-favorite-meal-at-the-end-of-the-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors,</p>

<p>By now, I hope you&rsquo;ve learned that when the day comes to a close, you should lower your calories, as your body is less active. One of the easiest ways to do that is by swapping out the starchy carbs with the fibrous carbs. This also keeps your insulin levels relatively low, resulting is less fat storage.</p>

<p>Today I want quickly share with you what <em>my</em> favorite meal looks like as the day comes to an end.</p>

<p><strong>This meal is really easy to make, takes less than 10 minutes of actual work, and burns your fat like crazy.</strong></p>

<p>So here&rsquo;s what you&rsquo;ll need:</p>

<ul>
<li>3 oz. salmon filet</li>
<li>1 red bell pepper</li>
<li>A bunch of asparagus</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Instructions:</em></p>

<ol>
<li><p>Set the oven to 450 degrees, and shove the salmon in there. If your salmon is frozen like mine, you don&rsquo;t need to wait for it to thaw. Just heat it for 30 minutes. If your salmon is already thawed, heat it for 20.</p></li>
<li><p>10 minutes before the salmons done, spray pan with olive oil and heat it up on medium.</p></li>
<li><p>Cut the asparagus stalks and throw them into the pan. Saute occasionally, for 5 minutes.</p></li>
<li><p>Cut the bell pepper and add that into the pan. Saute everything for 5 minutes.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>By now, the salmon should be done. Take it out of the oven and serve it with vegetables on the side. Feel free to garnish with whatever seasoning you like.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s what mine looks like:</p>

<p>Super easy, super clean, and super fat burning.</p>

<p>Enjoy this meal warriors.</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Weight Lifting Mistakes]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/22/top-3-weight-lifting-mistakes/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-22T16:12:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/22/top-3-weight-lifting-mistakes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors!<br/>
<br/>
Believe it or not, weight lifting when it comes to transforming your body isn’t about what exercises you do.<br/>
<br/>
It’s about <strong>HOW</strong> you do those exercises.<br/>
<br/>
I often get asked the question: <br/>
<br/>
“Ken, what kind of exercises do you do to get your [insert any muscle] so big?”<br/>
<br/>
And when I respond with my typical exercise, they tell me:<br/>
<br/>
“Really? That’s it? I do the same and I just can’t seem to grow my [insert same muscle] to be like yours.”<br/>
<br/>
When I ask them details about how they lift, that’s when I notice things start to fall apart. When it comes to achieving their goal of growing their muscles, they are simply lifting improperly.<br/>
<br/>
Today, I want to share with you 3 of the most common mistakes that I notice from those that I’ve come across asking for help.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>1. Lifting Too Heavy</strong></p>

<p>This one is the biggest mistake for some to admit. Look guys, just because you can swing the weight up, doesn’t mean that it’s helping your muscles grow. Weight lifting isn’t only about lifting the weight up. It’s about doing it properly for your goals. Our goal here is to grow our muscles. Swinging the weight up to meet the final destination isn’t benefiting you in any way. It might even result in an injury, putting you out of the game for a long time.</p>

<p>My advice: Leave your ego at the door before you walk in the gym. If you ever notice that you’re sacrificing your technique just to lift the weight up, rack it up and pick lighter weights, and then go back to focusing on lifting with the proper form. You don’t want to be the person who hurts yourself at the gym. Lifting heavy for your ego does nothing for your body.</p>

<p><strong>2. Lifting with Incorrect Tempo</strong></p>

<p>The proper tempo to contract and release your weight when you are trying to maintain or grow muscle mass, is by contracting for 1, holding the tension for 1 second at the peak, and then releasing for 3. <br/>
For example, if you’re performing shoulder raises, contract your shoulders by raising your arms up and out over a 1 second duration, holding for 1 second at the peak, and then slowly releasing your arms back down to its starting position over a 3 second duration.</p>

<p>If you cannot hold this contraction at the peak of the movement, or release over a period of 3 seconds, reread bullet point 1 about lifting too heavy.</p>

<p><strong>3. Lifting without Proper Muscle Contraction</strong></p>

<p>This one is one that I suffered with for a long time when I first started.</p>

<p>If you don’t feel the proper muscles contracting for the exercise that you’re doing, then you’re wasting really valuable time!</p>

<p>For example, did you know that when you’re doing dumbbell bicep curls, you feel the most contraction when you supinate your hand more by turn your pinky inwards towards you? Or for rope pushdowns, did you know that if you fully extend your forearms out and behind the side of your body, you obtain the maximum contraction?</p>

<p>With every rep, always ask yourself if you’re feeling your muscles properly contract. If the answer is no, make sure that you’re lifting with the proper form, and if necessary, reread bullet point 1 about lifting too heavy.</p>

<p>So what mistakes are you currently making?</p>

<p>And more importantly, <em>what will you do to correct these mistakes so that you don&rsquo;t any more waste valuable time at the gym?</em></p>

<p>Until then, train hard, and I&rsquo;ll see you on the other side.</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Reasons Why HIIT Will Help You Achieve Success]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/top-3-benefits-of-hiit-for-your-successful-journey/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-21T19:39:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/top-3-benefits-of-hiit-for-your-successful-journey</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey, what&rsquo;s going on warriors!<br/>
<br/>
Today, I want to talk about 3 huge advantages that HIIT (High Intensity Interval Training) has over steady-state cardio and how they will help you achieve success in your body transformation journey.<br/>
<br/>
If you are not already familiar with the fundamental difference between HIIT and steady-state cardio, make sure that you check out my post here first, before continuing on.<br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, let&rsquo;s get down to business.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>1. HIIT Is Great For Your Heart</strong><br/>
<br/>
When you’re doing steady state cardio, quite often, you can’t push yourself to your maximum work rate because you need to make sure your session lasts a long time. However, with HIIT, since your sessions are much shorter, you actually can push yourself hard enough such that your heart rate reaches 85% to 100% of your maximum heart rate. Raising your heart rate via exercise is a great way to reduce cholesterol, lower the risk of heart disease, and greatly improves your cardiovascular system.</p>

<p><strong>2. HIIT Is Less Mentally Draining</strong></p>

<p>Which would you rather choose? </p>

<p>60 minutes of jogging</p>

<p>OR&hellip;</p>

<p>10 minutes of HIIT</p>

<p>If you’re like most people, you would probably choose number 2. That makes sense. After all, 10 minutes of an activity that achieves more fat burn than 60 minutes of another is an incredible time saver.</p>

<p>But also, think about how mentally exhausting it is to consider doing 60 minutes of cardio. Just the thought of that makes ME extremely tired.</p>

<p>With shorter sessions, you become more motivated to power through your exercises and get on with the day. And when you’re more motivated, you’re more likely to stay consistent and achieve success in your journey.</p>

<p><strong>3. HIIT Is More Fun</strong></p>

<p>In steady-state cardio, you’re most likely just doing one motion over and over again at the same pace. There aren’t many variables, and you can easily get bored. If you find yourself pulling out a book and reading your favorite novel on the treadmill, then you’re already not going to make much progress, as you’re not even putting 100% of your focus on the workout.</p>

<p>In contrast, HIIT allows you to combine very different movements and exercises. You can easily create your own fun routines to do. Having a variety and mixing things up makes it much more engaging, and it makes it something that you can look forward to doing. And the more you do it, the more fat you&rsquo;ll burn!</p>

<p>If you’re still not convinced about all of the benefits of HIIT, just do a simple Google search on it and you’ll find a ton more info.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ll see you in the next post.</p>

<p>Cheers!</p>

<p>Your warrior companion, <br/>
Ken Yu </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know This Hormone to Reduce Belly Fat]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/the-key-hormone-to-reduce-belly-fat/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-21T14:20:09-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/the-key-hormone-to-reduce-belly-fat</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,<br/>
<br/>
Think about your usual day, and ask yourself this:<br/>
<br/>
How often do you feel stressed?<br/>
<br/>
You might think that’s a weird question to ask, especially when I’m supposed to tell you how you can get rid of your stubborn belly fat. <br/>
<br/>
But that question is actually extremely relevant. Because get this: <br/>
<br/>
When you’re stressed, your body actually stores more fat!</p>

<p>That’s right. Let me introduce you to the hormone responsible for this behavior: <strong>cortisol.</strong></p>

<p>Cortisol is your stress hormone. Your body releases it when you’re stressed.</p>

<p>Its primary goal is to “help” your body store fat. The only problem is, you don’t even have to eat for this process to happen. Once you stress, you jumpstart the cortisol hormone to start doing its dirty work.</p>

<p>What’s worse about this hormone is that the fat cells in your abdominal area are extremely sensitive to cortisol. In fact, your abdominal fat cells are 4 times more sensitive to storing fat than other cells in your body.</p>

<p>This is why it is so important to monitor our stress levels, not just for emotional benefits, but also for physical benefits.</p>

<p>Today, I’m going to share with you 5 ways that you can reduce your stress levels, some of which you can start doing right now.</p>

<div id="blog-link"></div>


<p><strong>1. Get at least 8 hours of sleep</strong><br/>
This may be hard for many people, but you have to realize that sleep is so important, not just for cortisol levels, but for your sanity levels as well. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9415946" title="Studies Show a 45% Increase in Cortisol Levels the Following Night">In fact, studies show that not having enough sleep causes your body to increase cortisol levels by as much as 45% the next evening.</a> So set an alarm at night to force yourself to stop whatever you’re doing and just go to sleep.</p>

<p><strong>2. Show Gratitude</strong><br/>
This one sounds weird, but a lot of the times, we don’t appreciate what we have around us. From our homes, our cars, and our loved ones, to the fresh air, clean water, and food sources. We kind of just…drag ourselves along day by day, not realizing what we have. <br/><br/>Take a moment out of your morning every day to really appreciate and be truly grateful for what you have in your life. It might help to imagine the kind of impact that certain things would have on your life if they were hard to access or didn’t exist.<br/></p>

<p><strong>3. Laugh</strong><br/>
If you’re not laughing every day, you’re not enjoying life! If you have a hard time finding funny things around you, then force yourself to laugh. Just laugh out loud for no reason! Try it right now!</p>

<p><strong>4. Meditate</strong><br/>
Last year, I started using the <a href="https://www.headspace.com/" title="Headspace App">Headspace App</a>. You’ve probably heard of it, and if you don’t have it, yet, I highly recommend you get it. Tuning in 10 minutes a day has helped me so much in becoming more grounded, centered, and focused on the things that I need to do, and less distracted by the millions of thoughts that go on in our heads on a daily basis.</p>

<p><strong>5. Surround Yourself With Positive Energy</strong><br/>
Choose to look at the glass half full instead of half empty so that you stop seeing the world from a problematic point of view. Surround yourself with happy people who look on the bright side. This will ultimately reduce stress, and thus, reduce cortisol levels.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Fat Burning Meal]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-20T15:06:22-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,<br/>
<br/>
I&rsquo;m going to cut straight to the chase here.<br/>
<br/>
In order to build a body that is lean and shredded, <strong>you need to consume lean proteins, fibrous carbs (vegetables), and starchy carbs!</strong><br/>
<br/>
  And what exactly does that look like?<br/>
<br/>
  <a href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/food-sources" title="Food Sources">On this page, I&rsquo;ve included a few examples of meals that I eat on a daily basis that have served as incredible fat burners for me throughout my entire journey.</a></p>

<p>Keep in mind that if you’re sensitive to carbohydrates, of if you’re trying to lose fat, you will want to lower your portion sizes for the starchy carbs and increase your portion sizes for the fibrous carbs.</p>

<p>  You will also need to adjust the portion sizes of each item above so that you eat the proper amount of calories for each meal, and that by the end of the day, you come close to your daily calorie target.  </p>

<p>Those who have my digital bundle of Your Warrior Transformation can plan out their meals with the proper calories and portion sizes in an instant with the provided spreadsheet. If this is something you’re interested in, be sure to grab a copy.  </p>

<p>Also, if you don’t know your lean proteins, fibrous carbs, or starchy carbs, be sure to visit this section of my blog. There, you will find my favorite food items among these categories to mix and match, so you can create your own fat burning meals!</p>

<p>  So go ahead and try eating these meals (or the ones you create) today. Let me know how you feel afterwards!   I look forward to hearing back from you.  </p>

<p>Your warrior companion, <br/>
Ken Yu </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quit Obsessing Over Your Weight]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/18/quit-obsessing-over-your-weight/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-18T12:58:47-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/18/quit-obsessing-over-your-weight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s frustrating.<br/>
<br/>
One morning, you step on the scale and record your body weight for the day.<br/>
<br/>
The very next day, under the same circumstances, after following every meal and exercise routine you&rsquo;ve planned, you step the on scale again, and guess what happens?<br/>
<br/>
You gain another five pounds.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>WTF?</strong> That number on the scale should be going down if you&rsquo;re doing everything correctly! Where is that extra weight coming from? What are you doing wrong?!</p>

<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/FlOHnTIv1mj2U" width="480" height="256.6530612244898" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p>The wheels in your head start spinning&hellip;</p>

<p>Was it from the higher sodium content of the foods you ate yesterday, causing your body to retain more water than usual?</p>

<p>Was it because of the fluid retention from your menstrual cycle?</p>

<p>Or, was it because you&rsquo;ve gained a bit of muscle throughout your body?</p>

<p>Maybe it was because the scale somehow got miscalibrated?</p>

<p>Or maybe there was even a blip in the earth&rsquo;s gravitational pull? Maybe I should step on the scale again&hellip;</p>

<p>You get the point. As you can see, there are just waaaaay too many factors that can affect the number on your scale. And unfortunately, there&rsquo;s nothing you can do to find out your exact weight.</p>

<p><strong>But that doesn&rsquo;t mean it&rsquo;s the end of the world.</strong></p>

<p>Keep in mind that your body transformation journey is about <em>changing the shape of your body.</em></p>

<p>So ultimately, do you really care about the number on the scale? Or <em>do you care more about how your body looks?</em></p>

<p>If you start your journey weighing 200 pounds, and two months later, you look in the mirror and you appear leaner and more muscular, but you haven&rsquo;t lost a single pound, are you really going to be frustrated that you just can&rsquo;t seem to get to 199 pounds?</p>

<p>Vice versa, if you start your journey weighing 200 pounds, and two months later, you&rsquo;re 190 pounds, but you look in the mirror and realize that you look even more flabby and less toned than you did before, are you really going to be happy that you lost those 10 pounds?</p>

<p>Bottom line is this: instead of obsessing over the number on the scale, start looking at your body in the mirror. Measure your body fat with calipers or simply pinch your belly fat with your fingers. If you feel like you have less fat than you did before, or if you feel like you look more toned and muscular, then that&rsquo;s what really matters!</p>

<p>Until then, continue envisioning the body that you want, keep doing the right things over and over, and enjoy the process! The results will come.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIIT It, Don't Quit It]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/14/hiit-it-dont-quit-it/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-14T10:49:39-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/14/hiit-it-dont-quit-it</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the best things that I love about HIIT, and that you will come to love as well, is that it is incredibly efficient. The HIIT routines that you will do will last no more than 10 minutes, and you can do them anywhere.<br/>
<br/>
This means, in just 10 minutes, you&rsquo;ll be able to crank up your metabolism and burn more calories overall than you would making your way to a gym and spending an hour doing the old and boring steady-state cardio on the treadmill or elliptical.<br/>
<br/>
The other great aspect about a 10 minute HIIT session is that, because it is only 10 minutes long, it is much less mentally exhausting compared to a long session of steady-state cardio. In fact, I get addicted to how quick and fun the routines get, that on some days, I&rsquo;ll even do multiple HIIT sessions. It may burn, and I&rsquo;ll sweat a lot, but damn, thats when I feel the most alive!</p>

<p>Needless to say, I am all about convenience and efficiency. I have a ton of other things that I need to get done in a day, and I&rsquo;m sure you do, too. So if I can invest in my health and physique anywhere in just 10 minutes, I will do it without hesitation.</p>

<p>What about you? Will you make excuses? Or will you just do it?</p>

<p>Come check out my existing routines <a href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/hiit" title="HIIT Routines">right here on this page</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Obsessing Over Calories]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/12/stop-obsessing-over-calories/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-12T13:28:54-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/12/stop-obsessing-over-calories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,<br/>
<br/>
It is essential to understand the three different macronutrients - fats, carbs, and proteins - and how they compose your daily calories.<br/>
<br/>
Too often, I see so many people do their due diligence in tracking their daily calories, but when I look at the contents of what they eat, it&rsquo;s something along the lines of &ldquo;half a Big Mac, 1 Twinkie, 2 chocolate chip cookies&rdquo; sprinkled with &ldquo;a few fries&rdquo; or &ldquo;salad.&rdquo;<br/></p>

<p>Yes, the calories in vs. calories out equation holds true to a certain extent. If you want your body weight to go down, then eat less calories than what you burn. If you want your body weight to go up, then eat more than what you burn.</p>

<p>But let me ask you this: are you really going after a magic number on the scale, or are you going after a great looking body?</p>

<p>Do you want to be bones covered in just fat, or do you want to be &ldquo;toned&rdquo; - having a sexy shape defined by your muscles with little fat?</p>

<p>Eating junk food constantly while keeping your calories below maintenance levels won&rsquo;t help you achieve your goal of getting the latter.</p>

<p>Don&rsquo;t get me wrong – you will lose weight, because you&rsquo;re definitely eating less, but ultimately, you will not get the desired body that you want because you&rsquo;re not feeding your body the right contents (think skinny-fat).</p>

<p>Similarly, if you’re trying to gain muscle, staying above your maintenance levels by eating junk food (dirty-bulking) will only give you a blob in the end (think buff-fat).</p>

<p>Let me present to you an analogy.</p>

<p>Imagine hiring a bunch of workers to help you build the house of your dreams. In order to build out your home, you need a lot of wood.</p>

<p>However, instead of supplying your workers with the wood that they need, you supply them with a bunch of incorrect raw materials like mud and hay.</p>

<p>Now, do you think they&rsquo;ll be able to build the house of your dreams?</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s the same concept when it comes to feeding your body the materials that it needs.</p>

<p>Even if you are diligent in counting your calories, if you continue eating whatever you want, you&rsquo;ll be trying so hard while eating for taste, that by the time you actually get to your target weight, you will still be just as out of shape as you were before you started your journey.</p>

<p>Was all of the energy spent holding back on eating that other half of the Big Mac really worth the half-ass result?</p>

<p>Was all of the time spent bulking up to your target weight really worth the round shape that you see in the mirror?</p>

<p>Regardless of whether or not you’re trying to gain weight or lose weight, your goal is to aim for a certain physique that you want your body to have.</p>

<p>This means that instead of obsessing over counting calories, you should pay more attention to the <strong>macronutrients</strong> that you are feeding your body.</p>

<p>As a guide:</p>

<ul>
<li>If your goal is to <strong>lose weight</strong>, <em>20% of your calories should come from fat, 40% of your calories should come from carbohydrates, and 40% of your calories should come from protein.</em></li>
<li>If your goal is to <strong>gain muscle</strong>, <em>20% of your calories should come from fat, 45% of your calories should come from carbohydrates, and 35% of your calories should come from protein.</em></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Dieting, Now!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/11/stop-dieting/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-11T21:55:36-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/11/stop-dieting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How many times have you or people you know claimed that they&rsquo;re starting a new diet, only to hear something like this:<br/><br/></p>

<blockquote><p>“This time, I&rsquo;m going to stick to my diet! No more carbs! I&rsquo;m going to cut them out completely for good and only eat 1000 calories a day.”</p></blockquote>

<p><br/>or<br/>
<br/></p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Hey, check out this new apple vinegar cider that I&rsquo;m drinking every day. It&rsquo;s helped me lose so much weight, and I barely have to do anything!”</p></blockquote>

<p>Probably way too often. And it&rsquo;s not their fault. Through technology and clever marketing tactics, diets like Paleo or Atkins, fat-burning supplements, and detox or cleansing diet fads have all caused a significant amount of noise and influenced the masses in an instant. “Lose 20 pounds in 10 days,” they say. Wow! Who wouldn&rsquo;t want the quick and easy fix?</p>

<p>In the world today, many gravitate towards the quick and easy solution to achieving the results that they want. Just take a quick look at your surroundings. How much of the technology around you was built to make your life easier so that you don&rsquo;t have to do anything anymore?</p>

<p>Unfortunately, these quick-fix solutions are often times not scalable, and when it comes to your health, it&rsquo;s simply not worth risking the unknown side effects. Remember that Rome was not built in a day, and neither should your weight loss journey be.</p>

<p>Take a moment to think about the shortcuts around you in life. Have you ever tried taking shortcuts to achieving what you wanted?</p>

<p>For example, how many people do you know who have illegally taken the HOV lane to beat traffic, only to get pulled over eventually by law enforcement?</p>

<p>If that concept is not clear enough, then imagine taking the stairs down from the top of a building without an elevator, and then imagine taking the shortcut - jumping off of the building. Which method do you think creates long-lasting results?</p>

<p>The same idea can be applied to shortcuts in weight loss. You may get the quick results that you seek by taking some magic pill or cutting out carbs completely, but over time, this solution won&rsquo;t scale. Eventually, when you snap back to reality, you’ll just gain back all of the weight that you&rsquo;ve lost, and then some, or even worse, permanently damage your body from the side effects of the supplements you took. Then, if you still have the chance, you&rsquo;ll have to start all over again, hopefully the right way next time. As John Wooden once said:</p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;If you don&rsquo;t have time to do it right, when will you have time to do it over?&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>Bottom line - if you want something, you have to work for it. Especially when it comes to your health, shortcuts are simply not worth the risk. That kind of a &ldquo;diet&rdquo; is not the lifestyle that you can afford to sustain.</strong></p>

<p>With that said, understand that only a part of your body transformation journey requires you to obtain the necessary information regarding nutrition and exercise, and harness this knowledge to construct a system that fits your lifestyle.</p>

<p>The bulk of your efforts throughout your journey requires you to actually execute upon your plan diligently with your utmost warrior mentality. You need to push yourself to do the things that you need to do, even when your mind is holding you back, begging you not to change, or dying for the easy way out. You need to short-circuit the limiting beliefs which exist in your mind, and you need to ignite the beliefs that you can and that you will. This is the warrior mentality.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to get off the amateur diet.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to quit being average.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to do it the right way.</p>

<p><strong>Start building the foundation of your transformation by developing a strong mindset. Then, take everything you learn, and tap into your warrior mentality to transform your body.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never Give Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/10/never-give-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-10T08:38:38-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/10/never-give-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What&rsquo;s going on Six Pack Warriors?<br/>
<br/>
Today I want to talk about <strong>persistence.</strong><br/>
<br/>
I&rsquo;m sure many of you have heard this topic so many times. But I wanted to try to give you another perspective on the matter.<br/>
<br/>
Take a moment to look at the living things around you. Guess what? Every one of those living things has more persistence than we do.</p>

<p>Whether it&rsquo;s your dog, your cat, your pet fish or hamster. Notice how they are so persistent in getting what they want. Sure, they might not be as smart as us, but they sure as hell don&rsquo;t give up trying to do something.</p>

<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/67BZPE8f0aPe0" width="480" height="360" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p>If you own a dog, you&rsquo;ll know exactly what I mean. No matter how many times I tell my dog to leave the kitchen because I&rsquo;m not going to feed her human food, she will always come over, sit beside me, and wait for the chance of my giving it to her.</p>

<p>And no matter how I try to hide her toy from her, she will always try to find ways to get to it. She never stops trying until she gets it.</p>

<p>The same thing can be said about plants. Look at how they persist in the way they grow. They find ways to bend, stretch, and curl so that they can get the maximum amount of exposure to a light source. Do you think they&rsquo;ll ever just give up suddenly? No way. Not until they die.</p>

<p>Having a higher level of intelligence is a double-edged sword. Sure, it has made us smarter, but it has also given us the ability to doubt ourselves more often. It has made us fear failure, to the point where we usually give up on our goal after a couple of attempts.</p>

<p>So as warriors, we need to shut off the part of our brain that&rsquo;s spewing out all of those limiting and negative thoughts, and we need to just go after the things we want with the utmost persistence and confidence.</p>

<div class="post-content-image-wrapper">
<img src="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/persistence.jpg" class="post-content-image" alt="Persistence"/>
</div>


<p>Until the day that you die, never ever give up on getting the things that you want in life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Cure Your Hangover In 10 Minutes]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/07/how-to-cure-your-hangover-in-10-minutes/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-07T09:32:53-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/07/how-to-cure-your-hangover-in-10-minutes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the most peculiar things that I discovered throughout my body transformation journey was this:<br/>
<br/>
Whenever I go out drinking the night before, drink a bit more than I should, and wake up the next day with a big hangover, for some weird reason&hellip;<br/>
<br/>
<strong>The hangover completely dissipates after I work out.</strong><br/>
<br/>
It&rsquo;s very counterintuitive, because usually when we are hungover, all we want to do is lie around in bed and rest up. We feel dizzy, weak, and maybe even nauseous. So naturally, we feel like all we can do is vegetate.</p>

<p>But friends, that&rsquo;s the beauty of thinking like a warrior. Even on the days when I&rsquo;m hungover, I still drag my ass out of the bed and hit the gym with my utmost focus and concentration. And the beautiful thing is, by the time I come home, my hangover just magically goes away.</p>

<p>As I think more and more about this, I realize that it makes perfect sense. By working out, we increase our metabolism, and thus, we increase our cells' processes. This means our body is able to flush the toxins out of our body much more quickly. Hangover? Gone.</p>

<p>See what happens when you think like a warrior?</p>

<p>And as I&rsquo;m getting older and older, this trick becomes more and more important, because my body&rsquo;s ability to metabolize alcohol weakens, and no matter how much water I drink to try to flush the alcohol out of my system, it just never seems to be enough. I&rsquo;d be pissing clear fluids, and my head would still feel dizzy.</p>

<p>So, throughout the years, from this discovery, I&rsquo;m going to share with you what I believe is the most efficient hangover cure that you should have in your journey as a warrior.</p>

<p>With that said, here is my 10 minute workout that will completely get rid of your hangover, guaranteed. Get ready guys, because it&rsquo;s going to be some intense high intensity interval training.</p>

<p>Here we go:</p>

<p><strong>Total time: 10 minutes</strong></p>

<p>Perform these exercises for 45 seconds straight, then take a 15 second rest. Repeat at least 10 times.</p>

<ul>
<li>1 Burpee With Push Up → 6 Mountain Climbers → 6 Jumping Lunges (Repeat for 45 seconds)</li>
<li>Rest (for 15 seconds)</li>
</ul>


<p>Try this out guys. I promise, if you ever wake up with a hangover, this is the best way you can get rid of it and get on with your day.</p>

<p>Cheers,<br/>
Ken</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Warrior Ways to Increase Your Metabolism]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/06/3-warrior-ways-to-increase-your-metabolism/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-06T20:06:53-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/06/3-warrior-ways-to-increase-your-metabolism</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to weight loss, one term gets thrown around quite often: <em>metabolism.</em><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Why is metabolism so important?</strong><br/>
<br/>
You probably already know that in order to lose weight, you need to be at a calorie deficit. And to be at a calorie deficit, you need to burn more calories than you consume.<br/>
<br/>
Well, one major way to burn more calories is by elevating your metabolism, which is the rate at which your body burns calories.</p>

<p><strong>So if you want to focus on burning calories, you need to focus on increasing your metabolism. Simple as that.</strong></p>

<p>Here, I&rsquo;m going to cover the three most important ways you can increase your metabolism.</p>

<p>No, I&rsquo;m not talking about eating tons of cayenne pepper or taking ice cold showers. That&rsquo;s for the amateurs.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m talking about real work. Yeah, that&rsquo;s right - the smart and efficient way. The warrior way.</p>

<p>So, let&rsquo;s get into it.</p>

<p><strong>1. Eat Smaller, Balanced Meals, More Frequently<br/></strong>
Eating more frequently in smaller meals not only helps curb your hunger, but when consumed with the proper macronutrients, it also helps keep your metabolism high. Your meals should consist of the correct macronutrient ratios - <strong>it must contain lean proteins and complex carbs</strong>.</p>

<p>In our body transformation book, if your goal is to maximize fat loss, we suggest that your macronutrient ratio should be 20% fat, 40% carbs, and 40% protein. If you are carb sensitive, you can also go with 20% fat, 35% carbs, and 45% protein.</p>

<p>If your body fat percentage is relatively low and if your goal is to maximize muscle growth, we suggest that your macronutrient ratio be 20% fat, 45% carbs, and 35% protein.</p>

<p>Make sure that you eat mostly lean proteins as your source of protein. This can be egg whites, chicken breast, turkey breast, any kind of white fish, or low fat dairy products.</p>

<p>For complex carbs, go with slow digesting carbs like oatmeal or brown rice. As always, include fibrous carbs (vegetables, beans) in the mix.</p>

<p><strong>2. Do HIIT<br/></strong>
HIIT, or High Intensity Interval Training, is a cardio technique that has been proven time and time again to be the most efficient way of burning fat.</p>

<p>In contrast to conventional, steady-state cardio, which burns calories only during the duration of your workout, <strong>HIIT training elevates your metabolism for a prolonged duration, causing you to continue to burn more calories even after your workout.</strong></p>

<p>So don&rsquo;t just walk or jog on the treadmill all day, every day. Mix it up and incorporate some HIIT routines into your workout session. For a list of my favorite routines, check out my YouTube channel here. I guarantee you, an hour after your HIIT session, you will still be sweating!</p>

<p><strong>3. Build Muscle<br/></strong>
This is a bit more of a touchy subject for females, who may feel a bit scared about building muscle. After all, it may not seem attractive for a woman to want to &ldquo;bulk up&rdquo; and look like the Incredible Hulk.</p>

<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/copwHGtEBC2Yg" width="480" height="265.18950437317784" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p>Relax.</p>

<p><strong>Building muscle is actually not that easy for women.</strong></p>

<p>For starters, women naturally have higher estrogen levels and lower testosterone levels. Lower testosterone levels make it much harder for women to actually gain as much muscle as fast as men can. Plus, the moment that you think you look too bulky, you can always cut down on the amount of weight that you lift.</p>

<p><strong>Having muscles also helps you shape your body!</strong></p>

<p>Muscles give your body definition. Imagine being skinny with a layer of fat without much muscle mass (AKA &ldquo;skinny-fat&rdquo;). While you may not look fat, you also don&rsquo;t look great, because your body&rsquo;s shape isn&rsquo;t backed by the muscles that you should have. If you want that toned, beach-body look, then you need to start going to the gym and lifting weights.</p>

<p>Lastly, and the most important part about building muscle, is that <strong>having more muscle mass directly increases your metabolism.</strong></p>

<p>The more muscle you have, the higher your metabolism will be. And the higher your metabolism is, the more calories you burn!</p>

<p>Imagine your muscles as the fire logs in your fireplace. The more you have, the more you burn!</p>

<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/QXMSWeZAW0C08" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe>


<blockquote><p>Imagine your muscles as the fire logs in your fireplace. <br/>The more you have, the more you burn.</p></blockquote>

<p>So there you have it, my top 3 tips to helping you increase your metabolism. Go ahead and start incorporating these tips into your routines if you haven&rsquo;t already. And again, for information on how you can incorporate these into your personalized body transformation system, check out my eBook <em><a href="https://gumroad.com/l/ivVMS" title="Your Warrior Transformation eBook">Your Warrior Transformation</a></em>.</p>

<p>Cheers!<br/>
Ken</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
