<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: mind over body | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/mind-over-body/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-14T09:12:11-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Dieting, Now!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/08/stop-dieting/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-08T21:55:36-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/08/stop-dieting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How many times have you or people you know claimed that they&rsquo;re starting a new diet, only to hear something like this:<br/><br/></p>

<blockquote><p>“This time, I&rsquo;m going to stick to my diet! No more carbs! I&rsquo;m going to cut them out completely for good and only eat 1000 calories a day.”</p></blockquote>

<p><br/>or<br/>
<br/></p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Hey, check out this new apple vinegar cider that I&rsquo;m drinking every day. It&rsquo;s helped me lose so much weight, and I barely have to do anything!”</p></blockquote>

<p>Probably way too often. And it&rsquo;s not their fault. Through technology and clever marketing tactics, diets like Paleo or Atkins, fat-burning supplements, and detox or cleansing diet fads have all caused a significant amount of noise and influenced the masses in an instant. “Lose 20 pounds in 10 days,” they say. Wow! Who wouldn&rsquo;t want the quick and easy fix?</p>

<p>In the world today, people tend to migrate towards the quick and easy solution to achieving the results that they want. Just take a quick look at your surroundings. How much of the technology around you was built to make your life easier so that you don&rsquo;t have to do anything anymore?</p>

<p>Unfortunately, these quick-fix solutions are often times not scalable, and when it comes to your health, it&rsquo;s simply not worth risking the unknown side effects. Remember that Rome was not built in a day, and neither should your weight loss journey be.</p>

<p>Take a moment to think about the shortcuts around you in life. Have you ever tried taking shortcuts to achieving what you wanted?</p>

<p>For example, how many people do you know who have illegally taken the HOV lane to beat traffic, only to get pulled over eventually by law enforcement?</p>

<p>If that concept is not clear enough, then imagine taking the stairs down from the top of a building without an elevator, and then imagine taking the shortcut - jumping off of the building. Which method do you think creates long-lasting results?</p>

<p>The same idea can be applied to shortcuts in weight loss. You may get the quick results that you seek by taking some magic pill or cutting out carbs completely, but over time, this solution won&rsquo;t scale. Eventually, when you snap back to reality, you’ll just gain back all of the weight that you&rsquo;ve lost, and then some, or even worse, permanently damage your body from the side effects of the supplements you took. Then, if you still have the chance, you&rsquo;ll have to start all over again, hopefully the right way next time. As John Wooden once said:</p>

<blockquote><p>If you don&rsquo;t have time to do it right, when will you have time to do it over?</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>Bottom line - if you want something, you have to work for it. Especially when it comes to your health, shortcuts are simply not worth the risk. That kind of a &ldquo;diet&rdquo; is not the lifestyle that you can afford to sustain.</strong></p>

<p>With that said, understand that only a part of your body transformation journey requires you to obtain the necessary information regarding nutrition and exercise, and harness this knowledge to construct a system that fits your lifestyle.</p>

<p>The bulk of your efforts throughout your journey requires you to actually execute upon your plan diligently with your utmost warrior mentality. You need to push yourself to do the things that you need to do, even when your mind is holding you back, begging you not to change, or dying for the easy way out. You need to short-circuit the limiting beliefs which exist in your mind, and you need to ignite the beliefs that you can and that you will. This is the warrior lifestyle.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to get off the amateur diet.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to quit being average.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to do it the right way.</p>

<p><strong>Start building the foundation of your transformation by developing a strong mindset. Then, take everything you learned, and use your warrior mentality to transform your body.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
