<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: fad diets | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/fad-diets/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-30T20:09:06-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don't Have To Eliminate Carbs]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/29/you-dont-have-to-eliminate-carbs/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-29T14:13:04-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/29/you-dont-have-to-eliminate-carbs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors!</p>

<p>You may have heard from the numerous fad diets these days that advise people to avoid carbs if they are looking to lose weight.</p>

<p>Listen guys - the truth is, <strong>you do NOT have to avoid carbs.</strong></p>

<p>You do not have to eliminate certain restaurants from your life. You do not need to go through the hassle of finding special ingredients to bake your favorite low/no carb treats.</p>

<p>In fact, there are simpler ways that allow you to achieve a lean, shredded physique, without sacrificing your social life or the foods that you love.</p>

<p>Remember, the best approach to transforming your body is by finding a method that scales for you and your lifestyle. There&rsquo;s no point of eliminating an entire macronutrient category if your lifestyle is filled with a bunch of social activities, or if you don&rsquo;t think that you can do this for the rest of your life.</p>

<p>Now, if you really do believe that you can completely avoid carbs for the rest of your life, then by all means, take on a low carb diet approach. But absolutely do your research first.</p>

<p>However, if you are not ready to give up your favorite foods, and if you are wondering how you can consume carbohydrates while still being on the right path to achieving your goal body, then read on. In this article, I will invest some time in you by teaching you exactly how carbohydrates affect your body&rsquo;s fat storage mechanisms. I will also show you what you can do to minimize your body from storing fat.</p>

<p>First, you must familiarize yourself with one special hormone that we have in our body: <strong>insulin</strong>.</p>

<h3>Insulin</h3>

<p>Insulin is a hormone, released by your pancreas, that controls the blood sugar levels in your body.</p>

<p>Whenever you eat and introduce carbohydrates into your bloodstream, your body breaks down the carbohydrates into the simple sugar glucose. As blood sugar levels rise, your body tries to remove glucose from your bloodstream by signaling your pancreas to release insulin. Insulin will then either prompt your cells to decide whether to absorb these sugars as energy for your liver and muscles, or to store them as fat.</p>

<p>The question is this:</p>

<blockquote><blockquote><p>How exactly can you tell insulin to store what you eat as energy for your liver and muscles, instead of as fat on your body?</p></blockquote></blockquote>

<p>To answer <em>that</em> question, we must now understand the term <strong>Glycemic Index (GI)</strong>.</p>

<h3>Glycemic Index</h3>

<p>GI is a term used to measure how quickly your body can convert the food that you eat to glucose that your body can use.</p>

<p>Foods with high GI spike your insulin levels, and foods with low GI allow for a more steady insulin response.</p>

<p>The higher your insulin levels, the more likely your body stores what you eat as fat. The lower your insulin levels, the less likely your body stores what you eat as fat.</p>

<p>So, the main idea is this:</p>

<blockquote><blockquote><p>If you want to prevent your body from storing fat, you should keep your insulin levels low. You can do this by eating foods with low GI. This creates a slow, steady insulin release.</p>

<p>If you want to gain a lot of fat on your body, you should keep your insulin levels high. You can do this by eating foods with high GI - foods that quickly become sugar the moment it hits your tongue. This creates a large insulin spike.</p></blockquote></blockquote>

<p>How do you know which foods cause a slow and steady insulin response, and which foods cause a rapid insulin spike? A complete list of foods and their GIs can be found <a href="http://www.the-gi-diet.org/lowgifoods/" title="List of GI Foods">here in this list</a>.</p>

<p>Most of the time, you want to keep your insulin levels low. You should never need your insulin levels to be high, otherwise your body would be storing everything you eat as fat.</p>

<h3>The One Exception - When High Insulin Levels Are Beneficial</h3>

<p>However, there is one exception to the rule where high insulin levels will result in high fat stores.</p>

<p>In fact, there is one instance where high insulin levels actually helps shuttle what you eat into your muscle and liver stores.</p>

<p>Can you think of a time when you would intentionally want your body to store the nutrients that you eat as energy for your liver and muscles?</p>

<p>This may sound a little crazy, but, how about <em>after exercising</em>?</p>

<p>See, after a workout, your muscle cells are depleted of energy. In this moment, it makes sense to create an insulin spike, because you need your body to quickly recover and gain back all of the energy that you have lost from working out. In fact, you actually want to create an insulin spike, because you want your body to quickly absorb the nutrients you eat into your muscle cells in order to replenish their energy levels.</p>

<h3>Putting It All Together</h3>

<p>So what does this mean?</p>

<p>Well, remember the burger that you thought you couldn&rsquo;t eat anymore?</p>

<p>Or the sweet fruits that you thought you had to eliminate completely for the rest of your life?</p>

<p>Guess what, you can still eat them! <strong>As long as you eat them right after an intense workout.</strong> Yes, this concept might sound novel, but:</p>

<blockquote><blockquote><p>To get what you want, you have to deserve what you want.</p></blockquote></blockquote>

<p>Now if you&rsquo;re thinking that you need to work out for hours before you can treat yourself to a slice of pie, I&rsquo;m going to blow your mind away by telling you that you can actually work out for as little as 6 minutes, and still eat whatever you like.</p>

<p>How? Just <a href="/blog/2017/04/14/hiit-it-dont-quit-it/" title="High Intensity Interval Training">visit my other post here</a> to find out more.</p>

<p>Until then, train hard, and take comfort in knowing that you can still eat your favorite foods without eliminating carbs.</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
