<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: analogy | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/analogy/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-06-25T15:21:26-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fat = Gasoline]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/06/24/fat-equals-gasoline/"/>
    <updated>2017-06-24T19:28:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/06/24/fat-equals-gasoline</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors,</p>

<p>You&rsquo;ve probably figured out by now that your body fat is a form of energy. Technically, it is a form of excess energy that your body can’t store inside our muscle cells.</p>

<p>Essentially, alongside carbs, fat is your body&rsquo;s fuel.</p>

<p>Just like how gasoline is your car&rsquo;s fuel (if you don&rsquo;t own an EV).</p>

<p>Right now, I want you to take a moment to think about what happens when you drive around in your (non-EV) car.</p>

<p>Specifically, <strong>think about when you would get the most mileage out of your road trip, and when you get the least.</strong></p>

<p>You may notice that you get the most mileage (MPG) when you think about traveling on the highway, and the worst when you think about crawling along in stop-and-go traffic.</p>

<p>Basically, you notice that you burn the least amount of fuel when you’re traveling at a very steady and constant speed, and you burn the most amount of fuel when you’re in extremely choppy, variable speeds.</p>

<p>In terms of driving, you’d probably opt for the steady-state driving speed. After all, you’d probably want to save yourself some money.</p>

<p>However, when it comes to burning fat on your body, you actually want to do just the opposite. You want to vary your speed at which you work throughout our exercise routine, just like that stop-and-go style of traffic, so that you can exhaust the most amount of fuel in the least amount of time.</p>

<p>And that’s why <a href="/blog/2017/04/21/top-3-benefits-of-hiit-for-your-successful-journey/" title="The Benefits of HIIT">HIIT (High Intensity Interval Training)</a> absolutely works.</p>

<p>I know, I know. I’ve been harping on the benefits of HIIT, but seriously, hear me out.</p>

<p>It’s worked for me, it’s worked for professional athletes, and it’s worked serious bodybuilders out there.</p>

<p>And if you’re looking to get chiseled, if you’re looking to get that nice, lean, shredded and muscular look, you’ll want to employ HIIT into your routines.</p>

<p>Just check out the sample routines that I have in the <a href="/hiit" title="HIIT Routines">HIIT section</a> of this blog, and spread a few of these routines throughout your week. I guarantee you that you WILL shred some fat.</p>

<p>Until next time, train hard, and get shredded. Cheers!</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
