<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: warrior | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/warrior/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-25T15:56:03-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Cure Your Hangover In 10 Minutes]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/07/how-to-cure-your-hangover-in-10-minutes/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-07T09:32:53-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/07/how-to-cure-your-hangover-in-10-minutes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the most peculiar things that I discovered throughout my body transformation journey was this:<br/>
<br/>
Whenever I go out drinking the night before, drink a bit more than I should, and wake up the next day with a big hangover, for some weird reason&hellip;<br/>
<br/>
<strong>The hangover completely dissipates after I work out.</strong><br/>
<br/>
It&rsquo;s very counterintuitive, because usually when we are hungover, all we want to do is lie around in bed and rest up. We feel dizzy, weak, and maybe even nauseous. So naturally, we feel like all we can do is vegetate.</p>

<p>But friends, that&rsquo;s the beauty of thinking like a warrior. Even on the days when I&rsquo;m hungover, I still drag my ass out of the bed and hit the gym with my utmost focus and concentration. And the beautiful thing is, by the time I come home, my hangover just magically goes away.</p>

<p>As I think more and more about this, I realize that it makes perfect sense. By working out, we increase our metabolism, and thus, we increase our cells' processes. This means our body is able to flush the toxins out of our body much more quickly. Hangover? Gone.</p>

<p>See what happens when you think like a warrior?</p>

<p>And as I&rsquo;m getting older and older, this trick becomes more and more important, because my body&rsquo;s ability to metabolize alcohol weakens, and no matter how much water I drink to try to flush the alcohol out of my system, it just never seems to be enough. I&rsquo;d be pissing clear fluids, and my head would still feel dizzy.</p>

<p>So, throughout the years, from this discovery, I&rsquo;m going to share with you what I believe is the most efficient hangover cure that you should have in your journey as a warrior.</p>

<p>With that said, here is my 10 minute workout that will completely get rid of your hangover, guaranteed. Get ready guys, because it&rsquo;s going to be some intense high intensity interval training.</p>

<p>Here we go:</p>

<p><strong>Total time: 10 minutes</strong></p>

<p>Perform these exercises for 45 seconds straight, then take a 15 second rest. Repeat at least 10 times.</p>

<ul>
<li>1 Burpee With Push Up → 6 Mountain Climbers → 6 Jumping Lunges (Repeat for 45 seconds)</li>
<li>Rest (for 15 seconds)</li>
</ul>


<p>Try this out guys. I promise, if you ever wake up with a hangover, this is the best way you can get rid of it and get on with your day.</p>

<p>Cheers,<br/>
Ken</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
