<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: weight training | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/weight-training/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-05T08:13:21-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[READ THIS Before You Switch Up Your Weight Training Routine]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/02/read-this-before-you-switch-up-your-workout-routine/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-02T15:33:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/02/read-this-before-you-switch-up-your-workout-routine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors!</p>

<p>When we weight train for muscular hypertrophy, it’s tempting to want to look for that next shiny work out exercise that will help us explode our muscles to the next level.</p>

<p>However, <strong>I want to take a moment to caution everyone from switching up lifting routines too frequently, because doing so when we think we are plateauing can actually slow down our progress.</strong></p>

<p>If you are plateauing, before switching up your routine, make sure that you are doing the following things correctly, both in the gym and outside of the gym.</p>

<h2>In the gym:</h2>

<h3>1. Lift With Proper Tempo</h3>

<ul>
<li>Make sure the concentric part of the motion lasts 1 second.</li>
<li>Make sure that you <strong>squeeze and hold at the peak for 1 second</strong>.</li>
<li>Make sure that the eccentric part of the motion lasts 2-3 seconds.</li>
</ul>


<p>If you can’t do the above, check your ego by lowering the weight.</p>

<h3>2. Lift With Proper Form</h3>

<h4>Make sure you feel the proper muscles contracting</h4>

<p>  For example:</p>

<ul>
<li>When you&rsquo;re doing chest presses, make sure that you really squeeze the chests together. One way to focus on this contraction is by trying to bring your wrists towards each other when you press.</li>
<li>When you&rsquo;re doing bicep curls, make sure that you really feel the peak contraction. One way to focus on this contraction is by bringing the pinky up towards you.</li>
<li>When you&rsquo;re doing any sort of leg movements, make sure to really squeeze those quads and hamstrings. Doing so will actually help you lift heavier as well.</li>
</ul>


<h4>Don’t just throw the weight up.</h4>

<p>  Again, contract your muscles to help bring it up. Avoid swinging, as you can actually injure yourself.</p>

<p><strong>You absolutely need a LOT of focus here.</strong> This means, with every single rep, pay close attention to HOW you are lifting. If you have trouble with any of the above tips, you are lifting too heavy, so lower the weight.</p>

<p>Also, <strong>track your progress.</strong> Doing so will mentally prepare you for the next session where you overload these muscles.</p>

<h2>Outside of the gym:</h2>

<h3>1. Make sure you are eating at a calorie surplus</h3>

<ul>
<li>Eat at about a 15% calorie surplus.</li>
<li>Do your due diligence in tracking your macronutrients.</li>
</ul>


<h3>2. Make sure that you are eating enough, especially in carbs</h3>

<ul>
<li>You need carbs for your lifts. For great sources of carbs as energy, <a href="/food-sources" title="Food Sources">check out my list of starchy carbs here</a></li>
<li>You need the carbs to help open up the floodgates of your muscle cells to help shuttle protein into them for recovery</li>
<li>Typically, aim for a 20% fat, 45% carbs, 35% protein macronutrient ratio. Remember, it’s not just about loading up on protein! You need more carbs than you do protein.</li>
<li>Don&rsquo;t dirty bulk. Keep in mind that you care about your final shape. Plus, the leaner you look, the more muscular you actually appear.</li>
</ul>


<p>If, after doing these things in and outside of the gym, you still realize that you cannot make any more progress, then and only then, is it time to switch up your routine.</p>

<p>I hope that helps, Warriors.</p>

<p>Until next time, train hard, and stay focused!</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
