<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: motivation | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/motivation/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-29T17:19:03-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Transformation Story]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/27/my-transformation-story/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-27T12:53:23-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/27/my-transformation-story</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It all started in the summer of 2010, during my freshman year in college.</p>

<p>I don’t exactly remember how it happened, but one day, I woke up with a little flame inside me and decided that I wanted these:</p>

<p><a href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/abs.jpg" alt="Courtesy of the abs guys from Shilin Night Market — Taipei" class="image-link-wrapper">
  <img src="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/abs.jpg"/ class="max-width-image">
</a></p>

<p>Who doesn’t, right? After all, six-pack abs basically turn heads anywhere.</p>

<p>As an engineer at heart, I was naturally drawn to scientific and systematic ways of doing things. So after some time googling around for how to get those abs, I had found a book that made sense to me and my body transformation desires:
<em><a href="http://amzn.to/2qbz82v" title="Burn the Fat, Feed the Muscle">Burn the Fat, Feed the Muscle</a></em> by Tom Venuto (<a href="https://itunes.apple.com/au/book/burn-the-fat-feed-the-muscle/id708413335?mt=11" title="iBooks version">iBooks version</a>). From that moment on, my life would change forever.</p>

<p>I couldn’t put down the book. First of all, it completely took a massive dump on all of the fat burning myths, which are so pervasive in the “Fat Loss” industry — myths like the “lose 10 pounds of fat in 10 days” magazines that you see in the supermarket’s checkout counters, the “magic pill” that you take that makes you lose your appetite, those cleansing and fasting diets along with long, boring sessions of cardio, the unsustainable no carb/Atkins diets, you name it.</p>

<center>
<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/l0MYIbjlBxxw60O8E" width="480" height="330" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe></center>


<p>Instead, it went into the science behind why you can’t target fat loss (like trying to do countless crunches to get rid of belly fat), and that to really get rid of fat, you really just have to burn more calories than you’re taking in. Simple, yet often overlooked.</p>

<p>Then, Tom began talking about the technicalities of getting shredded — increasing muscle mass, employing HIIT, exploiting our body’s hormones at certain times, and receiving proper nutrition with tricks like carb-cycling. At this point, my engineering brain was hooked. I actually got so excited that I began opening up spreadsheets to plan out my meals and workouts while reading along.</p>

<p><a href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/sheets.png" alt="Bodybuilding Spreadsheet" class="image-link-wrapper">
  <img src="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/sheets.png"/ class="max-width-image">
</a></p>

<p>Above all, the most important piece of advice that Tom gave in his book that made my transformation everlasting is the psychological aspect of his system. <strong>Achieving six-pack abs is no quick and easy solution, but rather a journey and process that takes time.</strong> The most effective way to achieve this goal and to make it last is by having not only the proper knowledge, but also a <strong>powerful mindset</strong>. That is, in order for me to transform my body forever, I must develop the mindset of a warrior in order to achieve this goal. And after reading the book, that little flame inside me turned into a bonfire. I began to believe so strongly, like a devout theist, that I would achieve that shredded look.</p>

<p>And I did, eventually. It took some time (more than most would be willing to wait for) and a lot of effort (more than most would be willing to put in when first starting out). Although the results didn’t come immediately, I stayed patient — I focused on the process and relentlessly followed the system: getting proper nutrition, logging my macros and workouts, rehearsing and practicing my routines mentally before heading to the gym, employing high intensity interval training and carb-cycling, and in general, finding a way to fit all of these little puzzle pieces into my existing lifestyle. </p>

<p>Gradually over time, the results came.</p>

<p>2 months later, I started to notice the small changes. I had achieved my 6 pack abs, but I was still pretty damn scrawny. So I decided that I wanted to bulk up and gain some muscle.</p>

<p>In the next 4 months, I trained heavily in the gym, while incorporating cardio into my workout routines.</p>

<p>Soon, I started noticing results. People around me started to see them, too.</p>

<p>In fact, those who said that I couldn’t do it started asking for advice.</p>

<p>I took all of these signals and fed them back into my system, creating a positive feedback loop that fueled more gains and helped me press the advantage.</p>

<p>Over the course of the following 6 months, I would then go on to <strong>gain over 56 pounds of muscle mass while maintaining my 6 pack abs.</strong></p>

<p>And by the 12th month of my body transformation journey, I had achieved what they call the &ldquo;<a href="http://www.bodybuildingweightprogram.com/golden-ratio/" title="Adonis Golden Ratio">Adonis Golden Ratio</a>.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Visually, here&rsquo;s my before and after:</p>

<p><a href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/beforeafter.png" alt="Before and after, 12 month transformation journey" class="image-link-wrapper">
  <img src="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/transformation_story/beforeafter.png"/ class="max-width-image">
</a></p>

<p>Did I stop there? Absolutely not. To this day (almost 7 years later), I continue to polish my craft, from bulking up and leaning down, to planning around those curveballs that life throws at me every now and then. It’s a never-ending journey, and there is always room to improve.</p>

<p>The best part about my journey is that the positive feedback never stops coming. Those who know me personally call me crazy for waking up at 4:30 in the morning to hit the gym before heading work. And just the other day, I bumped into an old high school friend who was shocked when she saw me, as she had remembered me as a scrawny kid, but was now calling me “swole.”</p>

<center>
<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/l2JhCfCM9pH5XoXPG" width="480" height="269" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe></center>


<p>Ultimately, bodybuilding has become a vital part of me and manifests itself beyond the bounds of the gym. In fact, it has become my platform and foundation for almost every aspect in my life — <strong>I apply the same principles of bodybuilding to those areas in which I aim to achieve success in.</strong></p>

<p>There’s a saying:</p>

<blockquote><p>Your mind is the athlete. Your body is just the tool.</p></blockquote>

<p>I really do believe that. Whatever goal it is that you want to achieve in life, you must start by believing that you will achieve it. Then, continuously build strong thoughts around that goal. Most importantly, take action by focusing on the process, and the results will naturally come.</p>

<p>Cheers guys!</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>

<p><em>P.S. - If you would like my step-by-step blueprint on transforming your body, grab a copy of my eBook</em> Your Warrior Transformation, <em>available in all available formats, as well as my body transformation spreadsheet, right here:</em>  <a href="https://gumroad.com/l/ivVMS" title="Your Warrior Transformation">https://gumroad.com/l/ivVMS</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Dieting, Now!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/11/stop-dieting/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-11T21:55:36-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/11/stop-dieting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How many times have you or people you know claimed that they&rsquo;re starting a new diet, only to hear something like this:<br/><br/></p>

<blockquote><p>“This time, I&rsquo;m going to stick to my diet! No more carbs! I&rsquo;m going to cut them out completely for good and only eat 1000 calories a day.”</p></blockquote>

<p><br/>or<br/>
<br/></p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Hey, check out this new apple vinegar cider that I&rsquo;m drinking every day. It&rsquo;s helped me lose so much weight, and I barely have to do anything!”</p></blockquote>

<p>Probably way too often. And it&rsquo;s not their fault. Through technology and clever marketing tactics, diets like Paleo or Atkins, fat-burning supplements, and detox or cleansing diet fads have all caused a significant amount of noise and influenced the masses in an instant. “Lose 20 pounds in 10 days,” they say. Wow! Who wouldn&rsquo;t want the quick and easy fix?</p>

<p>In the world today, many gravitate towards the quick and easy solution to achieving the results that they want. Just take a quick look at your surroundings. How much of the technology around you was built to make your life easier so that you don&rsquo;t have to do anything anymore?</p>

<p>Unfortunately, these quick-fix solutions are often times not scalable, and when it comes to your health, it&rsquo;s simply not worth risking the unknown side effects. Remember that Rome was not built in a day, and neither should your weight loss journey be.</p>

<p>Take a moment to think about the shortcuts around you in life. Have you ever tried taking shortcuts to achieving what you wanted?</p>

<p>For example, how many people do you know who have illegally taken the HOV lane to beat traffic, only to get pulled over eventually by law enforcement?</p>

<p>If that concept is not clear enough, then imagine taking the stairs down from the top of a building without an elevator, and then imagine taking the shortcut - jumping off of the building. Which method do you think creates long-lasting results?</p>

<p>The same idea can be applied to shortcuts in weight loss. You may get the quick results that you seek by taking some magic pill or cutting out carbs completely, but over time, this solution won&rsquo;t scale. Eventually, when you snap back to reality, you’ll just gain back all of the weight that you&rsquo;ve lost, and then some, or even worse, permanently damage your body from the side effects of the supplements you took. Then, if you still have the chance, you&rsquo;ll have to start all over again, hopefully the right way next time. As John Wooden once said:</p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;If you don&rsquo;t have time to do it right, when will you have time to do it over?&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>Bottom line - if you want something, you have to work for it. Especially when it comes to your health, shortcuts are simply not worth the risk. That kind of a &ldquo;diet&rdquo; is not the lifestyle that you can afford to sustain.</strong></p>

<p>With that said, understand that only a part of your body transformation journey requires you to obtain the necessary information regarding nutrition and exercise, and harness this knowledge to construct a system that fits your lifestyle.</p>

<p>The bulk of your efforts throughout your journey requires you to actually execute upon your plan diligently with your utmost warrior mentality. You need to push yourself to do the things that you need to do, even when your mind is holding you back, begging you not to change, or dying for the easy way out. You need to short-circuit the limiting beliefs which exist in your mind, and you need to ignite the beliefs that you can and that you will. This is the warrior mentality.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to get off the amateur diet.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to quit being average.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s time to do it the right way.</p>

<p><strong>Start building the foundation of your transformation by developing a strong mindset. Then, take everything you learn, and tap into your warrior mentality to transform your body.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
