<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: weight lifting | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/weight-lifting/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-08T20:40:30-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Weight Lifting Mistakes]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/22/top-3-weight-lifting-mistakes/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-22T16:12:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/22/top-3-weight-lifting-mistakes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors!<br/>
<br/>
Believe it or not, weight lifting when it comes to transforming your body isn’t about what exercises you do.<br/>
<br/>
It’s about <strong>HOW</strong> you do those exercises.<br/>
<br/>
I often get asked the question: <br/>
<br/>
“Ken, what kind of exercises do you do to get your [insert any muscle] so big?”<br/>
<br/>
And when I respond with my typical exercise, they tell me:<br/>
<br/>
“Really? That’s it? I do the same and I just can’t seem to grow my [insert same muscle] to be like yours.”<br/>
<br/>
When I ask them details about how they lift, that’s when I notice things start to fall apart. When it comes to achieving their goal of growing their muscles, they are simply lifting improperly.<br/>
<br/>
Today, I want to share with you 3 of the most common mistakes that I notice from those that I’ve come across asking for help.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>1. Lifting Too Heavy</strong></p>

<p>This one is the biggest mistake for some to admit. Look guys, just because you can swing the weight up, doesn’t mean that it’s helping your muscles grow. Weight lifting isn’t only about lifting the weight up. It’s about doing it properly for your goals. Our goal here is to grow our muscles. Swinging the weight up to meet the final destination isn’t benefiting you in any way. It might even result in an injury, putting you out of the game for a long time.</p>

<p>My advice: Leave your ego at the door before you walk in the gym. If you ever notice that you’re sacrificing your technique just to lift the weight up, rack it up and pick lighter weights, and then go back to focusing on lifting with the proper form. You don’t want to be the person who hurts yourself at the gym. Lifting heavy for your ego does nothing for your body.</p>

<p><strong>2. Lifting with Incorrect Tempo</strong></p>

<p>The proper tempo to contract and release your weight when you are trying to maintain or grow muscle mass, is by contracting for 1, holding the tension for 1 second at the peak, and then releasing for 3. <br/>
For example, if you’re performing shoulder raises, contract your shoulders by raising your arms up and out over a 1 second duration, holding for 1 second at the peak, and then slowly releasing your arms back down to its starting position over a 3 second duration.</p>

<p>If you cannot hold this contraction at the peak of the movement, or release over a period of 3 seconds, reread bullet point 1 about lifting too heavy.</p>

<p><strong>3. Lifting without Proper Muscle Contraction</strong></p>

<p>This one is one that I suffered with for a long time when I first started.</p>

<p>If you don’t feel the proper muscles contracting for the exercise that you’re doing, then you’re wasting really valuable time!</p>

<p>For example, did you know that when you’re doing dumbbell bicep curls, you feel the most contraction when you supinate your hand more by turn your pinky inwards towards you? Or for rope pushdowns, did you know that if you fully extend your forearms out and behind the side of your body, you obtain the maximum contraction?</p>

<p>With every rep, always ask yourself if you’re feeling your muscles properly contract. If the answer is no, make sure that you’re lifting with the proper form, and if necessary, reread bullet point 1 about lifting too heavy.</p>

<p>So what mistakes are you currently making?</p>

<p>And more importantly, <em>what will you do to correct these mistakes so that you don&rsquo;t any more waste valuable time at the gym?</em></p>

<p>Until then, train hard, and I&rsquo;ll see you on the other side.</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
