<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: persistence | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/persistence/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-21T11:44:18-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never Give Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/10/never-give-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-10T08:38:38-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/10/never-give-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What&rsquo;s going on Six Pack Warriors?<br/>
<br/>
Today I want to talk about <strong>persistence.</strong><br/>
<br/>
I&rsquo;m sure many of you have heard this topic so many times. But I wanted to try to give you another perspective on the matter.<br/>
<br/>
Take a moment to look at the living things around you. Guess what? Every one of those living things has more persistence than we do.</p>

<p>Whether it&rsquo;s your dog, your cat, your pet fish or hamster. Notice how they are so persistent in getting what they want. Sure, they might not be as smart as us, but they sure as hell don&rsquo;t give up trying to do something.</p>

<iframe src="//giphy.com/embed/67BZPE8f0aPe0" width="480" height="360" frameBorder="0" class="giphy-embed" allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p>If you own a dog, you&rsquo;ll know exactly what I mean. No matter how many times I tell my dog to leave the kitchen because I&rsquo;m not going to feed her human food, she will always come over, sit beside me, and wait for the chance of my giving it to her.</p>

<p>And no matter how I try to hide her toy from her, she will always try to find ways to get to it. She never stops trying until she gets it.</p>

<p>The same thing can be said about plants. Look at how they persist in the way they grow. They find ways to bend, stretch, and curl so that they can get the maximum amount of exposure to a light source. Do you think they&rsquo;ll ever just give up suddenly? No way. Not until they die.</p>

<p>Having a higher level of intelligence is a double-edged sword. Sure, it has made us smarter, but it has also given us the ability to doubt ourselves more often. It has made us fear failure, to the point where we usually give up on our goal after a couple of attempts.</p>

<p>So as warriors, we need to shut off the part of our brain that&rsquo;s spewing out all of those limiting and negative thoughts, and we need to just go after the things we want with the utmost persistence and confidence.</p>

<div class="post-content-image-wrapper">
<img src="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/images/posts/persistence.jpg" class="post-content-image" alt="Persistence"/>
</div>


<p>Until the day that you die, never ever give up on getting the things that you want in life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
