<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: mistakes | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/mistakes/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-26T13:50:41-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Big Mistakes You're Making In Your Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/26/the-3-big-mistakes-youre-making-in-your-diet/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-26T12:24:14-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/26/the-3-big-mistakes-youre-making-in-your-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors!</p>

<p>So one of the most common questions I’m asked when summer starts rolling around, is how to safely and naturally achieve a lean, toned physique, without sacrificing the foods that I love, or going on some kind of a restrictive diet.</p>

<p>Now, you’ve probably heard and seen from those around you that if you &ldquo;simply count calories&rdquo; then you’d be well on your way to getting leaner and maybe getting abs by the summer.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, this couldn’t be further from the truth.</p>

<p>In fact, it’s most likely the number 1 mistake that is holding you back from achieving long-lasting success in your weight loss journey.</p>

<p>Or what about cutting out carbs from your life?</p>

<p>Well, it sure doesn’t help that carbs are everywhere&hellip;</p>

<p>Fruits, vegetables, even great sources of energy like rice, oatmeal, and potatoes, all contain carbs.</p>

<p>Can you imagine yourself going on vacation and restricting carbs while trying to relax by the beaches at the same time?</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m sure it goes without saying that eliminating your favorite foods and restaurants for the rest of your life quickly leads to a kind of lifestyle that becomes very hard to scale, resulting in another failed diet and more wasted time.</p>

<p>Which is why today, I want to invest in your health and physique by teaching you the 3 biggest mistakes that are preventing you from obtaining success in your weight loss journey.</p>

<p>Just imagine being able to freely enjoy the meals that you love with your friends and family at your favorite local restaurants and social gatherings.</p>

<p>All of it, without feeling like you’re cheating, guilty, or falling off the wagon, while others wish they had your ability to easily craft your sexy summer body and maintain it all year round.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s these little success tips known by myself and other warriors that make all the difference between an enjoyable lifestyle, and an unscalable one. And when you do this right,</p>

<p>So if there&rsquo;s one blessing that I can share with you today, it is how to achieve your summer physique and keep it all year round, without ever feeling like you’re on a constraining diet. And if this is something that you want to learn how to do, I’d encourage you to watch my free training webinar right below.</p>

<p>I’ll be teaching you…</p>

<ul>
<li>How carbs can be your best friend, mentally and physically.</li>
<li>When to consume the right foods at the right times to avoid fat storage and increase fat burn</li>
<li>The difference between the way warriors perform cardio, and the way amateurs do</li>
<li>How to naturally burn more fat by cutting your exercise time down by as much as 90%</li>
<li>How to keep your ideal physique for life, without sacrificing the foods, restaurants, or social gatherings that you love</li>
</ul>


<p>If you’d like to start learning, you can watch the free, 75 minute training session right here:</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5q-yiP5tCRE" class="giphy-embed webinar" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
