<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: well-being | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/well-being/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-27T16:13:19-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know This Hormone to Reduce Belly Fat]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/the-key-hormone-to-reduce-belly-fat/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-21T14:20:09-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/21/the-key-hormone-to-reduce-belly-fat</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,</p>

<p>Think about your usual day, and ask yourself this:</p>

<p><strong>How often do you feel stressed?</strong></p>

<p>You might think that’s a weird question to ask, especially when I’m supposed to tell you how you can get rid of your stubborn belly fat.</p>

<p>But that question is actually extremely relevant. Because get this:</p>

<p><strong>When you’re stressed, your body actually stores more fat!</strong></p>

<p>That’s right. Let me introduce you to the hormone responsible for this behavior: <strong>cortisol.</strong></p>

<p>Cortisol is your stress hormone. Your body releases it when you’re stressed.</p>

<p>Its primary goal is to “help” your body store fat. The only problem is, you don’t even have to eat for this process to happen. Once you stress, you jumpstart the cortisol hormone to start doing its dirty work.</p>

<p>What’s worse about this hormone is that the fat cells in your abdominal area are extremely sensitive to cortisol. In fact, your abdominal fat cells are 4 times more sensitive to storing fat than other cells in your body.</p>

<p>This is why it is so important to monitor our stress levels, not just for emotional benefits, but also for physical benefits.</p>

<p>Today, I’m going to share with you 5 ways that you can reduce your stress levels, some of which you can start doing right now.</p>

<div id="blog-link"></div>


<p><strong>1. Get at least 8 hours of sleep</strong><br/>
This may be hard for many people, but you have to realize that sleep is so important, not just for cortisol levels, but for your sanity levels as well. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9415946" title="Studies Show a 45% Increase in Cortisol Levels the Following Night">In fact, studies show that not having enough sleep causes your body to increase cortisol levels by as much as 45% the next evening.</a> So set an alarm at night to force yourself to stop whatever you’re doing and just go to sleep.</p>

<p><strong>2. Show Gratitude</strong><br/>
This one sounds weird, but a lot of the times, we don’t appreciate what we have around us. From our homes, our cars, and our loved ones, to the fresh air, clean water, and food sources. We kind of just…drag ourselves along day by day, not realizing what we have. <br/><br/>Take a moment out of your morning every day to really appreciate and be truly grateful for what you have in your life. It might help to imagine the kind of impact that certain things would have on your life if they were hard to access or didn’t exist.<br/></p>

<p><strong>3. Laugh</strong><br/>
If you’re not laughing every day, you’re not enjoying life! If you have a hard time finding funny things around you, then force yourself to laugh. Just laugh out loud for no reason! Try it right now!</p>

<p><strong>4. Meditate</strong><br/>
Last year, I started using the <a href="https://www.headspace.com/" title="Headspace App">Headspace App</a>. You’ve probably heard of it, and if you don’t have it, yet, I highly recommend you get it. Tuning in 10 minutes a day has helped me so much in becoming more grounded, centered, and focused on the things that I need to do, and less distracted by the millions of thoughts that go on in our heads on a daily basis.</p>

<p><strong>5. Surround Yourself With Positive Energy</strong><br/>
Choose to look at the glass half full instead of half empty so that you stop seeing the world from a problematic point of view. Surround yourself with happy people who look on the bright side. This will ultimately reduce stress, and thus, reduce cortisol levels.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
