<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: calorie taper | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/calorie-taper/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-27T09:39:30-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Meal to Wrap Up the Day]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/25/my-favorite-meal-at-the-end-of-the-day/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-25T20:12:54-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/25/my-favorite-meal-at-the-end-of-the-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors,</p>

<p>By now, I hope you&rsquo;ve learned that when the day comes to a close, you should lower your calories, as your body is less active. One of the easiest ways to do that is by swapping out the starchy carbs with the fibrous carbs. This also keeps your insulin levels relatively low, resulting is less fat storage.</p>

<p>Today I want quickly share with you what <em>my</em> favorite meal looks like as the day comes to an end.</p>

<p><strong>This meal is really easy to make, takes less than 10 minutes of actual work, and burns your fat like crazy.</strong></p>

<p>So here&rsquo;s what you&rsquo;ll need:</p>

<ul>
<li>3 oz. salmon filet</li>
<li>1 red bell pepper</li>
<li>A bunch of asparagus</li>
<li>Some olive oil</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Instructions:</em></p>

<ol>
<li><p>Set the oven to 450 degrees, and throw the salmon in there. If your salmon is frozen like mine, you don&rsquo;t need to wait for it to thaw. Just bake it for 30 minutes. If your salmon is already thawed, bake it for 20.</p></li>
<li><p>10 minutes before the salmons done, spray pan with olive oil and heat it up on medium.</p></li>
<li><p>Cut the asparagus stalks and throw them into the pan. Saute occasionally, for 5 minutes.</p></li>
<li><p>Cut the bell pepper and add that into the pan. Saute everything for 5 minutes.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>By now, the salmon should be done. Take it out of the oven and serve it with vegetables on the side. Feel free to garnish with whatever seasoning you like.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s what mine looks like:</p>

<p>Super easy, super clean, and super fat burning.</p>

<p>Enjoy this meal warriors.</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
