<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: carbs | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/carbs/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-29T22:24:26-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Big Mistakes You're Making In Your Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/26/the-3-big-mistakes-youre-making-in-your-diet/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-26T12:24:14-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/05/26/the-3-big-mistakes-youre-making-in-your-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors!</p>

<p>So one of the most common questions I’m asked when summer starts rolling around, is how to safely and naturally achieve a lean, toned physique, without sacrificing the foods that I love, or going on some kind of a restrictive diet.</p>

<p>Now, you’ve probably heard and seen from those around you that if you &ldquo;simply count calories&rdquo; then you’d be well on your way to getting leaner and maybe getting abs by the summer.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, this couldn’t be further from the truth.</p>

<p>In fact, it’s most likely the number 1 mistake that is holding you back from achieving long-lasting success in your weight loss journey.</p>

<p>Or what about cutting out carbs from your life?</p>

<p>Well, it sure doesn’t help that carbs are everywhere&hellip;</p>

<p>Fruits, vegetables, even great sources of energy like rice, oatmeal, and potatoes, all contain carbs.</p>

<p>Can you imagine yourself going on vacation and restricting carbs while trying to relax by the beaches at the same time?</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m sure it goes without saying that eliminating your favorite foods and restaurants for the rest of your life quickly leads to a kind of lifestyle that becomes very hard to scale, resulting in another failed diet and more wasted time.</p>

<p>Which is why today, I want to invest in your health and physique by teaching you the 3 biggest mistakes that are preventing you from obtaining success in your weight loss journey.</p>

<p>Just imagine being able to freely enjoy the meals that you love with your friends and family at your favorite local restaurants and social gatherings.</p>

<p>All of it, without feeling like you’re cheating, guilty, or falling off the wagon, while others wish they had your ability to easily craft your sexy summer body and maintain it all year round.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s these little success tips known by myself and other warriors that make all the difference between an enjoyable lifestyle, and an unscalable one. And when you do this right,</p>

<p>So if there&rsquo;s one blessing that I can share with you today, it is how to achieve your summer physique and keep it all year round, without ever feeling like you’re on a constraining diet. And if this is something that you want to learn how to do, I’d encourage you to watch my free training webinar right below.</p>

<p>I’ll be teaching you…</p>

<ul>
<li>How carbs can be your best friend, mentally and physically.</li>
<li>When to consume the right foods at the right times to avoid fat storage and increase fat burn</li>
<li>The difference between the way warriors perform cardio, and the way amateurs do</li>
<li>How to naturally burn more fat by cutting your exercise time down by as much as 90%</li>
<li>How to keep your ideal physique for life, without sacrificing the foods, restaurants, or social gatherings that you love</li>
</ul>


<p>If you’d like to start learning, you can watch the free, 75 minute training session right here:</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5q-yiP5tCRE" class="giphy-embed webinar" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starchy Carbs VS. Fibrous Carbs - When to Eat What]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/30/starchy-vs-fibrous-carbs-when-to-eat-what/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-30T19:35:09-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/30/starchy-vs-fibrous-carbs-when-to-eat-what</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors!</p>

<p>Not all complex carbohydrates are created equal. Understanding the differences between the two classes of complex carbohydrates will help you know when you should be eating one over the other.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s begin by diving into the first main complex carbohydrate: <strong>starchy carbs.</strong></p>

<h3>Starchy Carbs</h3>

<p>Starchy carbs are carbs that contain high starch content. These are things like:</p>

<ul>
<li>bread</li>
<li>cereal</li>
<li>corn</li>
<li>oats</li>
<li>peas</li>
<li>rice</li>
</ul>


<p>For a more complete list of starchy carbs, check out <a href="/food-sources/" title="Food Sources List">this resource here</a>.</p>

<p>Starchy carbs are a great source of energy. When your body is active, you want to make sure that you properly nourish it with starchy carbs. Starchy carbs are able to raise your blood sugar levels, and thus, insulin levels, to help your cells absorb the sugars for energy.</p>

<p>However, it&rsquo;s highly unlikely that your body is always extremely active. In fact, when the day comes to a close, your body begins winding down, getting ready for relaxation. Your metabolism slows down, and your body&rsquo;s hormones become more sensitive to blood sugar levels.</p>

<p>During these times, it&rsquo;s important that we make sure to NOT create a high insulin response, something we usually get when we eat starchy carbs (<a href="/blog/2017/04/29/you-dont-have-to-eliminate-carbs/" title="Insulin Effect">remember that a high insulin response will actually cause the cells in our body to store the food in our body as fat</a>).</p>

<p>So does that mean that we just can&rsquo;t eat carbs at night?</p>

<p>Not necessarily. In fact, there&rsquo;s another type of complex carbohydrate that you <em>should</em> eat at night in order to avoid creating a rapid insulin spike: <strong>fibrous carbs.</strong></p>

<h3>Fibrous Carbs</h3>

<p>Fibrous carbs are carbs that contain a lot of dietary fiber. These are things like:</p>

<ul>
<li>vegetables</li>
<li>nuts</li>
<li>beans</li>
<li>certain fruits</li>
</ul>


<p>For a more complete list of fibrous carbs, check out <a href="/food-sources/" title="Food Sources List">this resource here</a>.</p>

<p>Fibrous carbs are a great source of replacement for starchy carbs as the day comes to a close. Because of their low GI score, they are recommended as one of the best foods to eat to maintain a slow, steady insulin response. Thus, it makes sense that if you want to help your body avoid storing fat, especially when its sensitive to carbs at night, that you swap out the starchy carbs with the fibrous carbs.</p>

<p>The other benefit of fibrous carbs is that it makes you feel extremely full due to its high fiber content. In fact, most fibrous carbs usually contain very few calories, so you can eat a lot, feel really full, and still be able to taper your calories to match your body&rsquo;s energy expenditure requirements at the end of the day.</p>

<h3>The Takeaway</h3>

<p>Understanding these two different types of complex carbohydrates will help you know when to feed your body the right types of carbs, depending on your activity level.</p>

<p>Just remember these two important points:</p>

<ul>
<li>During the times of your day when your body is active, consume meals that contain mostly starchy carbs, coupled with some servings of fibrous carbs.</li>
<li>During the times of your day when your body is not active (ie. towards night time), replace all starchy carbs with fibrous carbs.</li>
</ul>


<p>If you include these two rules into your meal plan while meeting your calorie targets, you will notice immense differences in the shape of your body.</p>

<p>I look forward to your progress. Until next time, train hard, and enjoy your meals. Cheers!</p>

<p>Your warrior companion,</br>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
