<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: macronutrients | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/macronutrients/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-21T11:46:18-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Fat Burning Meal]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-20T15:06:22-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey warriors,<br/>
<br/>
I&rsquo;m going to cut straight to the chase here.<br/>
<br/>
In order to build a body that is lean and shredded, <strong>you need to consume lean proteins, fibrous carbs (vegetables), and starchy carbs!</strong><br/>
<br/>
  And what exactly does that look like?<br/>
<br/>
  <a href="/food-sources" title="Food Sources">On this page, I&rsquo;ve included a few examples of meals that I eat on a daily basis that have served as incredible fat burners for me throughout my entire journey.</a></p>

<p>Keep in mind that if you’re sensitive to carbohydrates, of if you’re trying to lose fat, you will want to lower your portion sizes for the starchy carbs and increase your portion sizes for the fibrous carbs.</p>

<p>  You will also need to adjust the portion sizes of each item above so that you eat the proper amount of calories for each meal, and that by the end of the day, you come close to your daily calorie target.  </p>

<p>Those who have my digital bundle of Your Warrior Transformation can plan out their meals with the proper calories and portion sizes in an instant with the provided spreadsheet. If this is something you’re interested in, be sure to grab a copy.  </p>

<p>Also, if you don’t know your lean proteins, fibrous carbs, or starchy carbs, be sure to visit this section of my blog. There, you will find my favorite food items among these categories to mix and match, so you can create your own fat burning meals!</p>

<p>  So go ahead and try eating these meals (or the ones you create) today. Let me know how you feel afterwards!  I look forward to hearing back from you.  </p>

<p>Your warrior companion, <br/>
Ken Yu </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Obsessing Over Calories]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/12/stop-obsessing-over-calories/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-12T13:28:54-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/12/stop-obsessing-over-calories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,<br/>
<br/>
It is essential to understand the three different macronutrients - fats, carbs, and proteins - and how they compose your daily calories.<br/>
<br/>
Too often, I see so many people do their due diligence in tracking their daily calories, but when I look at the contents of what they eat, it&rsquo;s something along the lines of &ldquo;half a Big Mac, 1 Twinkie, 2 chocolate chip cookies&rdquo; sprinkled with &ldquo;a few fries&rdquo; or &ldquo;salad.&rdquo;<br/></p>

<p>Yes, the calories in vs. calories out equation holds true to a certain extent. If you want your body weight to go down, then eat less calories than what you burn. If you want your body weight to go up, then eat more than what you burn.</p>

<p>But let me ask you this: are you really going after a magic number on the scale, or are you going after a great looking body?</p>

<p>Do you want to be bones covered in just fat, or do you want to be &ldquo;toned&rdquo; - having a sexy shape defined by your muscles with little fat?</p>

<p>Eating junk food constantly while keeping your calories below maintenance levels won&rsquo;t help you achieve your goal of getting the latter.</p>

<p>Don&rsquo;t get me wrong – you will lose weight, because you&rsquo;re definitely eating less, but ultimately, you will not get the desired body that you want because you&rsquo;re not feeding your body the right contents (think skinny-fat).</p>

<p>Similarly, if you’re trying to gain muscle, staying above your maintenance levels by eating junk food (dirty-bulking) will only give you a blob in the end (think buff-fat).</p>

<p>Let me present to you an analogy.</p>

<p>Imagine hiring a bunch of workers to help you build the house of your dreams. In order to build out your home, you need a lot of wood.</p>

<p>However, instead of supplying your workers with the wood that they need, you supply them with a bunch of incorrect raw materials like mud and hay.</p>

<p>Now, do you think they&rsquo;ll be able to build the house of your dreams?</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s the same concept when it comes to feeding your body the materials that it needs.</p>

<p>Even if you are diligent in counting your calories, if you continue eating whatever you want, you&rsquo;ll be trying so hard while eating for taste, that by the time you actually get to your target weight, you will still be just as out of shape as you were before you started your journey.</p>

<p>Was all of the energy spent holding back on eating that other half of the Big Mac really worth the half-ass result?</p>

<p>Was all of the time spent bulking up to your target weight really worth the round shape that you see in the mirror?</p>

<p>Regardless of whether or not you’re trying to gain weight or lose weight, your goal is to aim for a certain physique that you want your body to have.</p>

<p>This means that instead of obsessing over counting calories, you should pay more attention to the <strong>macronutrients</strong> that you are feeding your body.</p>

<p>As a guide:</p>

<ul>
<li>If your goal is to <strong>lose weight</strong>, <em>20% of your calories should come from fat, 40% of your calories should come from carbohydrates, and 40% of your calories should come from protein.</em></li>
<li>If your goal is to <strong>gain muscle</strong>, <em>20% of your calories should come from fat, 45% of your calories should come from carbohydrates, and 35% of your calories should come from protein.</em></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
