<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: hiit | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/hiit/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-02T18:44:53-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIIT It, Don't Quit It]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/14/hiit-it-dont-quit-it/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-14T10:49:39-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/14/hiit-it-dont-quit-it</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the best things that I love about HIIT, and that you will come to love as well, is that it is incredibly efficient. The HIIT routines that you will do will last no more than 10 minutes, and you can do them anywhere.</p>

<p>This means, in just 10 minutes, you&rsquo;ll be able to crank up your metabolism and burn more calories overall than you would making your way to a gym and spending an hour doing the old and boring steady-state cardio on the treadmill or elliptical.</p>

<p>The other great aspect about a 10 minute HIIT session is that, because it is only 10 minutes long, it is much less mentally exhausting compared to a long session of steady-state cardio. In fact, I get addicted to how quick and fun the routines get, that on some days, I&rsquo;ll even do multiple HIIT sessions. It may burn, and I&rsquo;ll sweat a lot, but damn, thats when I feel the most alive!</p>

<p>Needless to say, I am all about convenience and efficiency. I have a ton of other things that I need to get done in a day, and I&rsquo;m sure you do, too. So if I can invest in my health and physique anywhere in just 10 minutes, I will do it without hesitation.</p>

<p>What about you? Will you make excuses? Or will you just do it?</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re still here, then I got a quick 6 minute HIIT routine right here:</p>

<div class="block-container">
  <div class="hiit-routine-container">
    <div class="video-embed routine-info-wrapper">
      <iframe class="hiit-embed" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VgWOP7eSyJA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>


<p>When you&rsquo;re done with that, come check out the rest of my existing routines <a href="/hiit" title="HIIT Routines">right here on this page</a>.</p>

<p>Train hard, warriors!</p>

<p>Your companion,<br/>
Ken Yu</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
