<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: fat burn | Six Pack Warriors Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/categories/fat-burn/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-30T20:02:26-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Six Pack Warriors]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[ken@sixpackwarriors.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Fat Burning Meal]]></title>
    <link href="http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal/"/>
    <updated>2017-04-20T15:06:22-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sixpackwarriors.github.io/blog/2017/04/20/how-to-create-a-fat-burning-meal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Warriors,</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m going to cut straight to the chase here.</p>

<p>In order to build a body that is lean and shredded, <strong>you need to consume lean proteins, fibrous carbs (vegetables), and starchy carbs!</strong></p>

<p>  And what exactly does that look like?</p>

<p>  <a href="/food-sources" title="Food Sources">On this page, I&rsquo;ve included a few examples of meals that I eat on a daily basis that have served as incredible fat burners for me throughout my entire journey.</a></p>

<p>Keep in mind that if you’re sensitive to carbohydrates, of if you’re trying to lose fat, you will want to lower your portion sizes for the starchy carbs and increase your portion sizes for the fibrous carbs.</p>

<p>  You will also need to adjust the portion sizes of each item above so that you eat the proper amount of calories for each meal, and that by the end of the day, you come close to your daily calorie target.  </p>

<p>Those who have my digital bundle of Your Warrior Transformation can plan out their meals with the proper calories and portion sizes in an instant with the provided spreadsheet. If this is something you’re interested in, be sure to grab a copy.  </p>

<p>Also, if you don’t know your lean proteins, fibrous carbs, or starchy carbs, be sure to visit this section of my blog. There, you will find my favorite food items among these categories to mix and match, so you can create your own fat burning meals!</p>

<p>  So go ahead and try eating these meals (or the ones you create) today. Let me know how you feel afterwards!   I look forward to hearing back from you.  </p>

<p>Your warrior companion, <br/>
Ken Yu </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
